let data = [
  {
    question:
      "Which built-in method calls a function for each element in the array?",
    options: ["while()", "do while()", "forEach()", "None of the above"],
    correctAnswerIndex: 2,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which built-in method returns the calling string value converted to lower case?",
    options: [
      "toLowerCase()",
      "toLower()",
      "changeCase()",
      "None of the above",
    ],
    correctAnswerIndex: 0,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which of the following function of Array object sorts the elements of an array?",
    options: ["toSource()", "sort()", "toString()", "unshift()"],
    correctAnswerIndex: 1,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which of the following function of Number object returns a string value version of the current number?",
    options: ["toString()", "toFixed()", "toLocaleString()", "toPrecision()"],
    correctAnswerIndex: 0,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which of the following function of String object creates a string to blink as if it were in a <blink> tag?",
    options: ["anchor()", "big()", "blink()", "italics()"],
    correctAnswerIndex: 2,
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is the HTML tag under which one can write the JavaScript code?",
    options: [
      "<javascript> ... </javascript>",
      "<scripted> ... </scripted>",
      "<script>...  </script>",
      "<js> ... </js>",
    ],
    correctAnswerIndex: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "Javascript is _____ language?",
    options: [
      "Dynamic computer programming language",
      "Object-oriented programming language",
      "Scripting language",
      "All the Above",
    ],
    correctAnswerIndex: 3,
  },
  {
    question: "What is the correct file extension for Javascript files?",
    options: [".java", ".js", ".javascript", ".script"],
    correctAnswerIndex: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "What is the output of ```js 33 == 33.0 ``` ?",
    options: ["False", "33", "True", "None of the above"],
    correctAnswerIndex: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "Choose the odd one",
    options: ["call()", "apply()", "bind()", "this"],
    correctAnswerIndex: 3,
  },
];


